Thank you so much for enrolling in my course.
Heel erg bedankt voor je inschrijving voor mijn cursus.
I am honored.
Ik ben vereerd.
Now, if you have any questions along the way while you are taking my training, please do not hesitate
Als je onderweg vragen hebt terwijl je mijn opleiding volgt, aarzel dan niet
to send me a text message or email me or whichever way that you prefer to contact me.
om me een sms of e-mail te sturen, of op welke manier dan ook.
Another thing I do want to ask you is that nowadays you do me ask you for a course rating or review
Iets anders wat ik u wel wil vragen is dat u mij tegenwoordig wel heel vroeg om een cursusbeoordeling of review
very early.
vraagt.
Probably you would watch my videos for 15 to 20 minutes and you will get a pop up window to rate my
Waarschijnlijk kijk je 15 tot 20 minuten naar mijn video's en krijg je een pop-up venster om mijn cursus te beoordelen.
If you think that my course does not worth five star yet, then please click on Skip and have it remind
Als je vindt dat mijn cursus nog geen vijf sterren waard is, klik dan op Overslaan en laat je herinneren aan het einde
you to the end of this course.
van deze cursus.
Then you should decide whether my course worth five star or not.
Dan moet u beslissen of mijn cursus vijf sterren waard is of niet.
So let's get started.
Dus laten we beginnen.